nappyboyonline.com 2013-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Sony Music

This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use and disclosure of your information in connection with your use of our websites, emails, and mobile applications (“Site” or “Sites”).  Sony Music Entertainment (“Sony Music”) is a wholly owned subsidiary of Sony Corporation of America. Information collected on this Site may be used in the manner described below by Sony Music Entertainment, our labels, agents, subsidiaries, trusted partners and affiliates acting on our behalf (collectively, “Sony Music”). When used herein, the terms “we”, “us” and “our” refer to Sony Music.

When this Privacy Policy uses the term “personal information,” we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as full name, street address, telephone number or email address.

Sony Music has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with[TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. Please note that TRUSTe provides this service only for information that is collected through Sony Music websites and does not cover information that may be collected through our mobile applications. TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions.

We encourage you to review the entire Privacy Policy. Please click on any of the links below to review that particular section.

* * *

Collection and Use of Personal Information

Social Networks/Online Communities

Transactions

Information Sharing

Choice/Opt-Out

Tracking Technologies

Security

Updating Your Personal Information

Consent to Processing

Additional Information

Changes to This Policy

Your California Privacy Rights

Questions About This Privacy Policy

* * *

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We may collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact information such as name, email address, street address, and phone number
  * Billing information such as credit card number and billing address
  * Demographic information such as age, gender, interests, country and zip code
  * Unique identifiers such as user name and password
  * Preference and other information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences and cell phone carrier
  * Location information such as your actual or approximate location

We or one of our trusted partners may use this information to:

  * Send you requested updates and newsletters about an artist, type of music or related special offers
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send a one-time email or e-card to your friends upon your request when you provide their email address
  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Respond to customer service requests, questions and concerns
  * Administer your account
  * Process information submitted with a job application
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Administer promotions and sweepstakes you enter and notify you of the results
  * Improve our marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis
  * Display content based upon your location and/or interests
  * To provide location services such as “tagging” and “check-in”

We also automatically collect information about your computer as you browse our Site(s).  Please see the Tracking Technologies section of this Privacy Policy. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active and as needed to provide you services.  We will use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

**Social Networks/Online Communities**

We enable you to create a profile for accessing blogs or online communities for sharing information such as messages, photos and videos.  Please note that we cannot control the actions of others with whom you may choose to share your pages and information.  We may also enable you to post content from some of our Sites to your profile on other social networks.  You can access these services from our Sites using Facebook Connect, Twitter, or other Open ID providers.  These services will authenticate your identity and allow you to post and share certain personal or other information with that site.  Please be aware that the privacy policy of that site will apply to any content you provide them in these instances.  We do not allow these services to provide any personal information or content back to our Sites or your profile with us unless you agree.  To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, [contact us here](http://hub.sonymusic.com/about/feedback.php). If we are unable to remove your personal information, we will respond to your request with the applicable reasons.

**Transactions**

You may purchase artists’ music or merchandise from some of our Site(s).  This Privacy Policy applies to any personal information you provide in connection with any such purchases.  In some instances, you may be directed to a third party site to initiate your transaction.  These third party sites will be clearly identified and link to their own privacy policies so you know which company is collecting your personal information.  You should refer to those policies for any privacy-related concerns regarding your purchase with them.

**Information Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We may provide your personal information to companies that help us with our business activities (e.g. processing credit card transactions, shipping your order, assisting us in Site operations, providing customer service, delivering email newsletters, etc.) or that assist us in improving our products, content, services or advertising.  These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services.

We may also share your personal information:

  * With Sony Music affiliates and representatives of our current recording artists
  * With affiliated Sony Group companies (i.e. any company in which Sony Corporation of America owns, directly or indirectly, 50% or more of its outstanding shares and any company with the name “SONY” as part of its trade name)
  * With reputable third parties in whose products or services we think you may have an interest, with your prior consent to do so
  * With representatives of former recording artists, who will be advised in advance that your consent is required for continued use
  * As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a government request
  * In connection with a corporate change including a merger, acquisition or sale of assets
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so

**Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving newsletters, updates or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails. Some Sites also allow you to change your email preferences within your online profile.

If you choose to join a mobile marketing list, please be aware that there are usually costs associated with receiving SMS (text) or MMS (multimedia) messages depending on your wireless carrier and plan. You should check with your mobile carrier to determine what charges apply before signing up to receive our updates via your mobile phone. If you would like to stop receiving messages from us on your mobile phone, please reply to the message with “STOP.” You may also contact your wireless carrier for additional information on receiving or stopping mobile messages.

If you have previously enabled your computer or mobile device to send us location information, you may be able to opt-out from further allowing us to access such information by changing the settings on your computer or mobile device or by uninstalling the application.

**Tracking Technologies**

We and our third party partners may automatically collect information as you browse our Site(s) such as the domain name, Internet Service Provider, browser type and version, mobile device ID, operating system and device type, average time spent on our Site(s), pages viewed, information accessed, the Internet Protocol (IP) address you use to connect to the Internet and related geographical information about your computer or mobile device. Such information is sometimes referred to as web analytics and/or clickstream data.

We and our third party partners use cookies and other technologies such as web beacons to keep track of your visits, preferences and profile information.  This information is used to make our Site(s) easier to use, improve our advertising, and to provide you with a more personal and convenient experience. For example, we may use this information to store some of your preferences or to provide you with tailored advertisements related to your specific interests. Additionally, should you choose to enroll, we and our third party partners may use this information to allow you to participate in one of our fan rewards programs. To learn more about the use of cookies in online advertising, including how to manage or delete them [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/learn_more.asp).

We and some of our third party partners use Flash cookies to store some of your preferences or personal information.  For more information on Flash cookies and how to manage privacy and storage settings [click here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html).

In some of our email messages, we use “click-through URLs” or pixel tags to determine whether the email has been opened and to measure the effectiveness of our customer communications.  This data may also be used to gauge your interest in particular topics, so we can deliver a more relevant, personal and convenient user-experience.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive billing information on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). If you choose to use a third party payment option to pay for your order, its privacy statement and security practices will apply to your information.  We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and after receipt. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Updating Your Personal Information**

Our Sites may offer different methods for updating your personal information. To review and update your personal information on artist marketing Sites, please log in to your profile/account on each Site where you have registered.

To update your billing or shipping information for purchases, please follow the customer service instructions in your order confirmation email.

If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us by [clicking here](http://hub.sonymusic.com/about/feedback.php).

**Consent to Processing**

Our Sites are operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States. By using our Sites, or providing us with any information, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in the United States, a jurisdiction in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen.

**Additional Information**

Widgets – Our Site(s) may include interactive mini-programs that provide specific services from another company (e.g., displaying digital news feeds, playing music, “liking” or sharing content, etc.), often referred to as widgets. You may have the opportunity to submit personal information, such as your email address, for collection through a widget. A widget may also use browser or Flash cookies and/or collect clickstream and usage data. Information collected by a widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

Links to Other Site(s) – Our Site(s) includes links to other site(s) whose privacy practices may differ from those of Sony Music.  If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any site you visit.

Children – We do not attempt to collect any personal information from those under the age of 13. If you feel that we have unknowingly collected information from someone under the age of 13, please [contact us](http://www.sonymusic.com/about/feedback.php) immediately and this information will be removed.

For more information on how to protect your children online:

**Visit  [www.OnGuardOnline.gov](http://www.onguardonline.gov/) for social networking safety tips for [parents](http://www.onguardonline.gov/topics/social-networking-sites.aspx) and [youth](http://www.onguardonline.gov/topics/safety-tips-tweens-teens.aspx).**

**Changes To This Policy**

By using our Site(s), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time and, as such, we encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If we make a material change to the way in which we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will send an email to users who have provided an email address or post a notice on our Site(s) prior to the change becoming effective.  Your continued use of the Site(s) after a revised version of this Privacy Policy has been posted will signify your consent to the terms of such revised policy.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 provides you the right to receive (a) information identifying any third party(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the preceding calendar year, your personal information for that third party’s direct marketing purposes; and (b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed.  To obtain such information free of charge, please write to us at the address below, or [submit your request here](http://hub.sonymusic.com/about/feedback.php). We will respond to these requests within thirty (30) days. Requests that come to us by other means may result in a delayed response.

**Questions About This Privacy Policy**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact Sony Music. You can contact us about this Privacy Policy by writing us:

Sony Music Entertainment 550 Madison Avenue, Room 2316

New York, NY 10022

Or you can [click here](http://www.sonymusic.com/about/feedback.php) to submit feedback online.

If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should [contact TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns TRUSTe provides this service only for information that is collected through Sony Music websites and does not cover information that may be collected through our mobile applications.
